profits25.com 2015-05-25

# PROFITS 25

### PRIVACY POLICY

**Purpose of the privacy policy of the Profits25.com website**  
This privacy policy of the website deals with the handling of the personal information of identification which is collected when you visit the site and when you are using the services of the site, as described in this privacy policy.  
This privacy policy applies neither to the practices of companies which Profits25 does not own or control, nor to people that Profits25 does not employ or direct, including particularly the advertising partners of the resource website or sponsoring third party to whom you provide information. Profits25 is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other websites to which you choose to connect from its website or from the resource site.  
Profits25 encourages you to examine each site's privacy policy and disclaimers so that you may understand and consent to how they may collect, use and share your personal information.

**Information collection and use**  
Profits25 does not collect any personal information of identification when you access the home page of the website and when you navigate it.

**Exchanging and supplying information**  
Profits25 may send your personal identification information to third parties when:  
\- we respond to subpoenas, court orders or procedural acts.  
\- we think it necessary, as established in full freedom, to investigate, prevent or take action against illegal activities, suspected frauds, emergency situations involving potential risks and threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Use of Profits25 or as required by law.

**Third party’s advertising**  
Other companies which display banners on resource site pages may set and access their cookies on your computer. The use of their cookies by other companies is subject to their own privacy policies, not to this one.

**Security**  
We have implemented technical and organizational measures designed to protect your personal information from accidental loss, unauthorized access and use, alteration or disclosure. However the Internet is an open system and we cannot guarantee that an unauthorized third party cannot circumvent these measures or use your personal data for illegal purposes.  
If you communicate with Profits25 by e-mail, you should note, that the secrecy of e-mailing communication is not certain. When you send by e-mail sensitive and confidential messages or information which are not encrypted, you accept the risk of this uncertainty and the possible lack of privacy on the Internet.

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
This policy can be amended if need be. If we alter our privacy policy in any way we will post the changes here. Please revisit this page from time to time to review any changes that may have been made, so as to keep informed of the information that we collect and how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we exchange it with any third party. If we make substantive changes to the way we use your personal information, we will keep you informed by posting a prominent announcement on the website.
